Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XIII is arranged in 111 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XIII. CITY CENTRAL BODIES
  - Sub-Series 212-0. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. General, 1960-1962 (Box 49a, Folder 10)
      1960-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - 213-0(a). Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.), 1951-1959 (Box 49a, Folder 11)
      Dec. 1951-Dec. 1959.
    - 213-0(a). Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.), 1945-1951 (Box 49a, Folder 12)
      1945-Nov. 1951.
    - 213-0(a). Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.), 1939-1944 (Box 49a, Folder 13)
    - Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.), 1937-1938 (Box 49a, Folder 14)
    - Jurisdiction. Disposition of jurisdictional dispute with International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.) by American Federation of Labor (A. F. of L.) (1937) Denver Convention, 1937-1941 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.)-New York Harbor, 1937-1938 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.)-Exhibits, data, etc. in connection with New York Harbor dispute and hearings before President's Emergency Board, 1937 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.), 1933-1936 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.)-Presque Isle Docks, Toledo, Ohio, 1934-1942 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - 213-0(c). Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.), 1935-1944 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.), 1921-1930 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railway Telegraphers-New Orleans, Texas & Mexico Railway, 1944-1947 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railway Telegraphers, 1948-1949 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      Dec. 29, 1948-Aug. 1949.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railway Telegraphers, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      Aug. 1948-Dec. 28, 1948.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      Jan. 1948-July 1948.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1946-1947 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      May 1946-Dec. 1947.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      Aug. 1945-April 194651.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1944-1945 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Dec. 1944-July 1945.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1942-1944 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      1942-Aug. 25, 1944.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      Aug. 26, 1944-Nov. 30, 1944.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1952-1959 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Aug. 1952-59.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1949-1952 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      Sept. 1949-July 1952.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers-Correspondence with G. E. Leighty, 1946-1948 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers-Southern Pacific-Teletype Operators, 1944-1947 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers-Replies to circular letter of Dec. 16, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      Dec. 16, 1944.
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers-Replies to circular letter of June 9th, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers (O. R. T.)-General-O. R. T. Submissions to National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1941-1942 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers (O. R. T.), 1944 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers (O. R. T.)-Special Jurisdictional Committee, 1939-1942 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers (O. R. T.)-Use of phone and operation of teletype machines, 1938-1942 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 213-3. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers-Canadian Pacific Railway (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 213-8. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      Aug. 17, 1932.
  - Sub-Series 213-11. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Maintenance of Way Employees-New York Central, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 213-21. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Maintenance of Way Employees-Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Railroad Company, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 213-27. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1921-1928 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      1921 and 1928.
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1938-1954 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen-Railway Express Agency (B.R.T.-R.E.A.), 1930-1936 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 213-30. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1924-1954 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-General, 1954-1957 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      1954-Dec. 31, 195753.
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-General, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      March 1953-Dec. 1953.
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-General, 1951-1953 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      1951-Feb. 1953.
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-General, 1947-1950 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      April 1947-50.
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-General, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      1947 March
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Teamsters), 1929-1931 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Teamsters), 1926-1928 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Teamsters), 1921-1925 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1953-1954 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-Detroit, Michigan, 1953-1954 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      July 8, 1953-Dec. 1954.
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-Detroit, Michigan, 1952-1953 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      1952-July 7, 1953.
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1953-1954 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - 213-30(F2C). Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Railway Express Agency, 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - 213-30(F2). Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Railway Express Agency, 1941-1942 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      Nov. 1941-42.
    - 213-30(F2). Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Railway Express Agency, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      April 1941-Oct. 1941.
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (West Coast)., 1930-1942 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-Interpretation of Scope Rule, 1939-1941 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1932-1938 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.), 1954 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      Jan. 1954-July 1954.
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1952-1954 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Carloading Companies, 1936-1946 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Carloading Companies, 1936-1950 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Carloading Companies-Seattle, Washington, 1936-1941 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Railway Express Agency, 1946-1947 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (I. B. of T.)-General, 1939-1942 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1941 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Railway Express Agency, 1948-1950 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Railway Express Agency, 1939-1946 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Railway Express Agency, 1942-1945 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Railway Express Agency, 1939-1941 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Testimony-Universal Carloading vs. Universal Independent Union, 1941 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Teamsters-Detroit Stock Yards Company-Michigan Central, 1941-1942 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 213-35. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Maintenance of Way (M. of W.)-C.C.C(?) & St. L.(?), 1939 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 213-38. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen (B. of R. T.). General, 1937-1953 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 213-40. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Waterfront Check Clerks-International Longshoremen's Association (I. L. A.), 1924-1955 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 213-42. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railway Telegraphers, 1925 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      Jan. 19, 1925.
  - Sub-Series 213-45. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1927 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 213-46. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Association of Machinists (Railroads), 1947-1950 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      May 1947-50.
    - Jurisdiction. International Association of Machinists (Railroads), 1954-1956 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      March 1954-56.
    - Jurisdiction. International Association of Machinists (Railroads), 1929-1930 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Jurisdiction. International Association of Machinists (Railroads), 1951-1954 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      1951-Feb. 1954.
    - Jurisdiction. International Association of Machinists (Railroads), 1932-1947 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      1932-April 1947.
  - Sub-Series 213-47. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railway Conductors, 1929-1953 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 213-48. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Union of Steam and Operating Engineers, 1930-1956 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 213-51. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1930 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 213-52. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1930 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 213-54. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1931 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 213-55. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks-International Longshoremen's Association, 1931-1932 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 213-56. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's Association-Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company, 1931 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 213-57. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks-Order of Railroad Telegraphers-New York West Chester and Boston Railroad, 1931 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 213-58. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers-Railway Express Agency, 1931 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 213-59. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks-Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1931-1932 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 213-61. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, 1944-1948 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, 1944-1956 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America-Leading Stockkeepers, 1933-1945 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, 1933-1943 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 213-63. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railway Conductors-Railway Express Agency, 1933 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 213-66. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1947-1957 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1933-1946 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 213-68. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Association of Machinists-Railway Express Agency (R.E.A.), 1934-1954 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 213-69. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1935-1953 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 213-71. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1936-1950 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 213-72. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers and Helpers, 1937-1956 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 213-73. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1937-1955 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 213-74. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Shop Crafts-Southern, 1937-1940 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 213-75. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Shops Crafts-Canadian National, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      1937 June 22
  - Sub-Series 213-76. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Shop Crafts-Various Railroads, 1937-1949 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 213-77. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Stenographers & Accountants Union Federal, Local No. 20940, 1937-1942 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 213-78. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Union of Elevator Constructors, Operators and Starters, 1937-1939 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 213-79. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. American Train Dispatchers' Association, 1938-1957 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 213-80. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Union of Operating Engineers, 1938-1939 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 213-81. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 213-82. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders and Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers of America, 1939-1957 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 213-83. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Amalgamated Association of Street Railway and Motor Coach Employees, 1939-1955 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 213-84. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Hotel & Restaurant Employees International Alliance, 1939-1954 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 213-85. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps), 1949-1957 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps)-Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal, 1940-1949 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps), 1948 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      April 1948-Dec. 1948.
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps), 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      Sept. 1942-43.
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps), 1946-1948 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      March 1946-48.
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps), 1944-1946 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      1944-Feb. 1946.
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps), 1942 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      Jan. 1942-Aug. 1942.
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps), 1939-1941 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps)-Memphis Union Station, 1942-1948 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Jurisdiction. United Transport Service Employees of America-CIO (formerly International Brotherhood of Red Caps)-St. Paul Union Depot, 1941-1947 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Red Caps-Representation of Red Caps in Cities of 100,000 and less, 1939-1943 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Red Caps, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Red Caps, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Red Caps-"Representation of Red Caps", 1937 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 213-86. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Associated Warehouse Unions of North America, 1939-1943 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 213-87. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1946-1957 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Jurisdiction. Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1939-1945 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 213-88. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Building Service Employees' International Union, 1941-1957 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 213-89. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. National Council of Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1944-1952 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Jurisdiction. National Council of Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1941-1942 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 213-90. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1951-1955 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      Aug. 1951-55.
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1948-1951 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      Nov. 1948-July 1951.
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1948 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      March 1948-Oct. 1948.
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union)-New England Area, New York City, 1941-1947 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1946-1948 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      May 1946-Feb. 1948.
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1943-1946 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      1943-April 1946.
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union) Cashen-Murray Conferences, 1942-1946 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America-Pacific Coast, 1941-1947 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1941-1946 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1941-1946 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1941-1946 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1941-1946 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad, 1941-1946 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-Detroit and Kansas City, 1941-1945 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (formerly United Railroad Workers Industrial Union, CIO)-General, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 213-91. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, CIO, 1941-1956 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 213-92. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 213-93. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Maintenance of Way Employees, 1945-1957 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      Nov. 1945-57.
    - Jurisdiction. Maintenance of Way Employees-General, 1933-1945 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      1933-Oct. 1945.
    - Jurisdiction. Maintenance of Way (M. of W.) Employees-General, 1920-1923 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 213-94. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Sleeping Car Conductors, 1942-1948 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 213-95. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, 1942-1949 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 213-96. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Switchmen's Union of North America, 1942-1953 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 213-97. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Shop Crafts. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 213-98. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. District 50, United Mine Workers of America, 1950-1956 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      Oct. 1950-56.
    - Jurisdiction. District 50, United Mine Workers of America, 1945-1950 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      Aug. 1945-Sept. 195060.
    - Box 60 does not exist. (Box 60)